hillstax.org 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy

##  Hillsborough County Tax Collector Public Information Disclaimer

If our Privacy Statement changes, we will post those changes on this page, so our users are aware of what information is collected, how it is used and under which circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.  Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes.

All content on this website, including but not limited to text, logos, buttons, icons and images, is property of the Hillsborough County Tax Collector.

###  User Acceptance of Terms of Use

Thank you for visiting the Official Web Site of the Hillsborough County Tax Collectors Office.  By accessing or using this site or any information, materials and data contained in the pages within this site, the user hereby agrees to and accepts the current terms and conditions ("[Terms of Use](http://www.broward.org/Terms/Documents/Broward.orgTermsOfUse.pdf "Terms of Use")") for use of this site. The Hillsborough County Tax Collector reserves the right to amend and update these [Terms of Use](http://www.broward.org/Terms/Documents/Broward.orgTermsOfUse.pdf "Terms of Use") from time to time.

This User Agreement is between you (or you on behalf of the person or entity that you represent, such entity hereafter referred to as "You," and in the possessive as "Your"), the Hillsborough County Tax Collector (the "Tax Collector") with whom You transact business through this site, and Grant Street Group as the designated service provider of the Tax Collector. Hillsborough.county-taxes.com is a web site (the "Web Site") used for accessing information and services of the Tax Collector.

You agree that You will not use any device, software or program to interfere with proper operations of the Web Site. You further agree that You will not use, nor allow anyone to use on your behalf, any robot, spider or other similar device to monitor or copy any pages of the Web Site or any content or information accessible through this Web Site.

You agree to take reasonable efforts to ensure that any electronic files or information You transmit through the use of the Web Site will be free from viruses or other code designed to interfere with the proper functioning of data information systems.

When accessing the Web Site, You must use software, including a web browser, that supports a data security protocol compatible with the protocol required for the Web Site.

You agree that the information you provide through the Web Site will be accurate.

You may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e., surveys or emails). Your choice to not participate will have no effect on your ability to access information on the Hillsborough County Tax Collector’s web site.

###  Privacy Statement:

Your privacy is important to us.  The Hillsborough County Tax Collector will do everything reasonably possible to protect your information using technology and good business practices.  Any personal information requested or gathered via this site will be used only for purposes necessary to conduct government business with you.  It will not be traded, sold, or given to any other party except as specifically allowed or required by law.

Persuant to Florida's Government-in-the-Sunshine and Open Government Laws all persons are entitled to information regarding the affairs of Florida government and the official acts and policies of those who represent them as public officials and public employees.

Information obtained by the Hillsborough County Tax Collector is considered a public record by law, and it must be disclosed upon request unless specifically [confidential and exempt from disclosure by law](http://floridarevenue.com/opengovt/Pages/public_records.aspx#confidential_info).

###  General Disclaimer:

The accuracy of the information provided on this website is not guaranteed for legal purposes. Changes occur daily to the content. To obtain the most current information, please contact our office.

The certified Tax roll records contained in this site reflect property ownership as of the date of certification and may not reflect current ownership. The most current ownership information can be obtained from the Hillsborough County Property Appraiser's Office.

###  E-mail Disclaimer:

Statement required by Section 668.6076, Florida Statutes: Under Florida Law, email addresses are public records. If you do not want your email address released in response to a public-records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.

However, e-mail addresses provided to the Hillsborough County Tax Collector’s Office by a taxpayer for tax administration purposes on a return, report, account, or declaration are confidential and exempt from disclosure under section 213.053(2), Florida Statutes, and may not be released pursuant to a public records request.

###  Information Collection and Use:

The Tax Collector's Office collects information from our website users and customers. We may collect or store information for statistical purposes. This information does not identify you personally. Only the following information is automatically collected and stored about your visit:

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
  * The date and time you access our site;
  * The pages you visit; and
  * If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.

We use this information to help us make the site more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.

If you choose to provide us with personal information – by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through the website – we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We only share the information you give us with another government agency if your inquiry relates to that agency, or as otherwise required by law. The Hillsborough County Tax Collector does not collect information for commercial marketing.

###  Automatic Data Collection:

The Tax Collector's Office website has features that automatically collect information from customers, to deliver content specific to customers' interests and to honor their preferences. This information assists us in creating products and services that will serve the needs of our customers. We make every effort to maintain the privacy of data collected from visitors to our website subject to or as required by applicable law.

For example, we use "cookies," a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies benefit the user by saving time while on our website. If users reject the cookies, they may be limited in the use of some areas of our website. The use of cookies enables our office to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience on our website.

For our internal purposes, we gather date, time, browser type, navigation history and IP address of all visitors to our website. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally. We use this information for our internal security audit log, trend analysis and system administration, and to gather broad demographic information about our user base for aggregate use.

Other than as set forth above, we make every effort to not share personally identifiable information with other companies; apart from those acting as our authorized agents in providing our product(s)/service(s), and which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to an official public records request, a court order, a subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or government property. Users should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without permission.

We may share aggregate information, which is not personally identifiable, with others. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information.

###  Data Retention:

Pursuant to Florida Statutes 119.021 (2) (a) The Division of Library and Information Services of the Department of State shall adopt rules to establish retention schedules and a disposal process for public records.  (b) Each agency shall comply with the rules establishing retention schedules and disposal processes for public records which are adopted by the records and information management program of the division.

###  Site Security:

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this government computer system employs commercial software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used for no other purposes and are scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with State guidelines for records management and retention.

Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
